<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>♦ Life on Chen&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://yccyangchen.github.io/posts/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ♦ Life on Chen&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:20:10 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yccyangchen.github.io/posts/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Girls&#39;s Night</title>
      <link>https://yccyangchen.github.io/posts/life/girlsnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:20:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yccyangchen.github.io/posts/life/girlsnight/</guid>
      <description>I felt so energetic today. I have to admit that I didn&#39;t work today. After today&#39;s daily meeting, my colleague，A chatted me. He mentioned that he was still busy setting up his new laptop but assured me he would let me know when he finished so he could assign me a new task. Additionally, I checked the master branch; it hasn&#39;t been updated by O yet. So, I had some free time today. Two colleagues who are somewhat responsible for me will be on a two-week and three-week vacation this month. I suppose I can inquire about the posiibility of becoming a working student when they return. I had a one-hour call with my old friend Sisi in China. She was one grade higher than me at my bachelor&#39;s university,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workday</title>
      <link>https://yccyangchen.github.io/posts/life/workday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 23:33:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yccyangchen.github.io/posts/life/workday/</guid>
      <description>Ich bin erschöft heute, da arbeitete ich ganz Tag 8 Stunden im Büro. Am Morgen met ich eine Kolligin N von mir in Frankfurt Hbf. I&#39;m exhausted today because I did work 8 hours in office today. During this 8 hours, I attended 3 meetings, contacted with 7 colleagues(online and offline, working and eating). I was CC for 14 times! But the real number of the Emails that I needed to check is only 4. I can tell my colleagues had a busy day today, since today is kind of important for release preparation but some of responsible persons are on holiday this month. There was one email literally saying(based on my understanding), come on someone please check this issue, the team we are cooperating is hard to handle&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
